nextstop.com 2009-12-14

# Privacy Policy | nextstop.com

## Privacy Policy

_Last updated: November 2009_

This policy applies to nextstop.com®, a site ("Site") provided by nextstop.com, Inc.

### Information we collect and how we use it

In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

  * **Information you provide** : When you sign up for an account with nextstop.com, we ask you for personal information (such as your username, email address and an account password). You do not need to register for an account or provide any personal information to us in order to use some features of the Site, such as browsing recommendations.

  * **Cookies** ; When you visit nextstop.com, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters to your computer - that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people use the site.

  * **Log information** : When you access nextstop.com, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website.These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

  * **Login location** : When you sign in to nextstop.com, we use your approximate physical location (based on the Internet Protocol address of your computer) to provide more relevant suggestions to you, such as places, guides or other members in your city or region. We will not use or store a location more specific than the city/region level for you without your explicit permission.

  * **User communications** : When you send email or other communications to nextstop.com, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

  * **Links** : nextstop.com may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our technology and customized content.

  * **Other sites** : This Privacy Policy applies to nextstop.com only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed in recommendations or other external links you may find on our site. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

nextstop only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

  * Providing our Site to users, including the display of customized content;

  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our Site;

  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and

  * Developing new services.

nextstop.com processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and may in the future use servers in other countries. 

### Choices for personal information

When you sign up for nextstop.com, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some nextstop.com features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

You can decline to submit personal information to nextstop.com, in which case you may not be able to use all of the features of the Site.

### Information sharing

nextstop.com will only share personal information with other companies or individuals outside of nextstop.com in the following limited circumstances:

  * When we have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.

  * When we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of nextstop.com, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can view the [Adify Privacy Policy](http://adify.com/privacy-policy) or the [Google Ads Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) which also includes information on how to opt out of Google advertising programs.

If nextstop.com becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who looked at a particular recommendation. Such information does not identify you individually.

Please contact us through our feedback form or at the address below for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.

### Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to nextstop.com employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

### Data integrity

nextstop.com processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

### Accessing and updating personal information

When you use nextstop.com, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

### Enforcement

nextstop.com regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or nextstop.com's treatment of personal information by contacting us through our feedback form or by writing to us at

nextstop.com  
attn: Privacy Policy  
650 Townsend St, Suite# 310  
San Francisco, CA 94110  
USA 

When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is our policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between nextstop.com and an individual.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site or at

nextstop.com  
attn: Privacy Policy  
650 Townsend St, Suite 310  
San Francisco, CA 94110  
USA
